matchclass.com 2017-05-12

# MatchClass

## Privacy Statement

### Privacy Policy for MatchClass.com

MatchClass.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices for this web site: http://www.MatchClass.com We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. MatchClass.com does not collect information on our web site visitors such as names, addresses, telephone numbers or e-mail addresses, unless you specifically give MatchClass.com that information. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Cookies

This site uses no cookies of any type. Other websites and companies with a theme similar to ours may use cookies on their website. Cookies are often used for advertising purposes. We do not have control or rights over the actions of these cookies. 

### Log Files/Web Traffic Reporting

We use web site traffic reporting services to solely track the search engines on our server and keep the reports for internal use; we do not use these reports to identify individual users except in cases of deliberate misuse of our systems. We do not share our server usage logs with third parties. 

### Registration

In some areas of this site, you will be asked to provide information that will used to follow-up with you on more information about a school, course, or contact form. Your participation is completely optional. The information is only used internally and only provided to the school you wish to Receive information from.
